Mark Primiano

Los Angeles, CA • (323) 854-4083 • hurricaneprimo@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Authentic connector who finds opportunities for creative problem solving in high-stress situations. Dedicated learner, constantly striving to be the best version of myself. Alive to the needs of others; able to create seamless, stress-free customer experiences.

- 15 seasons of assisting diverse patrons (accessible needs, community outreach, celebrities) at a world class concert arena
- Successfully created, produced and performed a full live show at a local Los Angeles comedy venue

SKILLS & CERTIFICATIONS

Ticketmaster, Tessitura, Archtics, MS Outlook, MS Word, Google Suite, Final Draft

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

ADA Department, Box Office & Customer Service Representative 2013 through present Hollywood Bowl - LA Philharmonic

Main point of contact for venue ticketing and accessibility services, specializing in assisting patrons with disabilities with venue logistics in a complex, 18k capacity venue.

- Manage daily presale parking passes, and consolidate all of the unsold passes for pickup by the Parking Department
- Generate nightly map of accessible patrons and coordinate with the house manager to reseat patrons accordingly.
- Troubleshoot accessibility issues between nightly opening of venue and show start; coordinating with ushers to help patrons navigate the complex space under tight timelines
- Field inquiries from accessible patrons, assisting with future show purchases and provide general customer service
- Assist accessible patrons with navigating the venue, providing a seamless theater-going experience
- Send marketing emails to 500 ADA season ticket subscribers; handle collections calls for payments

Box Office & Customer Service Representative 2003- 2013 Main point of contact for venue patrons; subject-matter expert on ticketing, performance schedule and venue navigation for venues ranging from 2500 to 18k patrons.

Hollywood Bowl - LA Philharmonic— 2003, 2008- 2013 Walt Disney Concert Hall - LA Philharmonic— 2004-2005 Dolby (Kodak) Theater— 2005-2007 Pantages Theater— 2007-2009

- Sold, organized, and scheduled daily venue tours At Dolby Theater and Disney Hall for groups of 25 people; tours happened every 20 minutes during peak season
- Organized and distributed will call tickets and assisted patrons with lost tickets Hosted

ticketing lottery presentation for high-demand shows; represented venue and presented winners with tickets in front of a live audience

• Staffed the "problem room"; helped to correct ticketing issues and provided high-level customer service to satisfy the needs of disappointed guests, including season subscribers • Consolidated third party ticket sales (Group sales, Goldstar, Groupon, etc.) with internal system for ticketing pick-up, creating seating assignments and accommodating guest requests as • Processed telesales ticket orders, and organized for performance pickup

Field Recruiter 2000-2003 Nielsen/National Research Group (now owned by Stagwell)

• Canvassed local areas to identify diverse audience members for major motion picture screenings, recruiting 5 to 50 people per screening

Actor (Theater, Film, Television, Commercial, Improv) Present Various

Work includes:

- Groundlings Sunday Company Member
- Talk of the Town- Series Regular
- Mark Primiano- Still Trying- Performer, Writer, Producer & Promoter
- World of Warcraft Voiceover Actor
- Waiting for Godot -- Lead Actor

EDUCATION & TRAINING

Bachelor of Architecture, University of Miami

Groundlings Theatre & School, Los Angeles, CA Writer's Lab & Advanced Training

HONORS AND AWARDS

Member, Groundlings Sunday Company 2011